indiagoldrate.com 2016-01-30

# Gold | Gold Rate | Gold Rates | Gold price | Gold prices | Gold Rate latest | price of gold | goldprice| Gold Rate India | Gold Rate Chennai | Gold Rates Mumbai,Gold Rate Today, Delhi,Hyderabad Kolkata

We understand your concern about the personal information you submit on our web-site. It can be appreciated that there has to be a fine balance between the need to provide better, personalized and customized service to you and at the same time to protect your personal details. We appreciate the trust you have in us that we shall not misuse your personal information in any way.

This document explains every aspect of our Privacy Policy to you. Your visit and actions undertaken on our site will be governed by the following policy. Firstly we don't store any information like credit card nombers given by you. It is separately stored by facebook.com

We reserve the right to add, modify, delete or change the contents of this privacy policy as may be felt necessary by us though the changes will be consistent with the spirit of the terms presented below.

**Information Collected**

To enable you to place an order on our site, we need to have the following basic information about you: Your First Name, Your Last Name, Your Address, City, Zip code, State, Country, Phone Number and Contact E-mail address.

Apart from this, our systems gather certain details about your computer's internet connection like your IP address when you visit our site. Your IP address does not identify you personally. We use this information to deliver our web pages to you upon request, to customise our site as per your interest, to calculate the number of visitors on our site and to know the geographic locations from where our visitors come.

We do not allow any unauthorized person or organization be it other members, visitors, and anyone not in our organisation to use any information collected from you.

**Information Sharing**

Probably this is the most important question in your mind as to with whom do we share your information? The answer to this question is that we do not rent, sell, barter, or give away your information to anyone. To some extent, information has to be passed on to the courier companies, credit card processing companies, vendors, etc. to enable them to perform their functions related to your order fulfillment. Apart from this normal business requirement, information may also be needed to be shared with law authorities, for fraud detection, and for the safety of our site, employees, management, users, members and other affiliates associated with us.

**Information Usage**

The most important usage of the information collected from you is your email which is used to inform you that your order has been confirmed/executed. Your email is also used to inform you for your customer service related queries and for any newsletters sent. All other information collected is confidentially stored and will not be disclosed unless needed as per the requirement of the law authorities or in case of any disputes.

**Cookies Usage**

�Cookies� are used to gather your unique interests when you visit our site. They let us know which products you are interested in, which pages you visit and to generate information that helps us to make the site better. Using cookies we can recognize repeat visitors and facilitate your visit. A cookie cannot gather data from your computer or hard disk by itself. Most browsers have a facility to turn off the cookie feature and to delete cookies from your computer. Doing so may restrict certain functionality of our site but will not hamper us in any substantial manner.

**Links with other sites**

Our site may contain links which may lead you to other sites which may have their own privacy policy over which we have no control. Please understand that once you leave our site, our privacy policy will no longer apply. E.g.. facebook.com
